Guide to the Robert A. Caro Archive [DATE]–2021 MS 3203
New-York Historical Society
- Series XI. Scrapbooks, 1952-2021 (bulk, 1974-2020)
  - Scrapbook 8, 1983, 1985 (Box [XI-06])
    [106] "Riverdale Ramblings," Riverdale Press, April 21, 1983.
    [107] "Personalities" [Charles S. Robb, Lyndon Johnson's son-in-law], Washington Post, April 23, 1983.
    [108a] "Caro will speak at Yonkers library," Riverdale Press, May 5, 1983.
    [108b] "Yonkers Public Library invites you to an evening with Award-Winning Author Robert A. Caro, Monday, May 9, 1983."
    [108c] Letter from Jacqueline E. Miller, Director, Yonkers Public Library, May 10, 1983.
    [109] Letter from [illegible] on Graduate School and University Center of the City of New York stationery, Ph.D. Program in English, May 11, 1983.
    [110a] Letter from Susan Scherreik, May 10, 1983.
    [110b] Susan Scherreik, "Author: Lyndon Johnson no saint," Morristown Daily Record, [May 9, 1983].
    [111] "Eighth Annual Nassau/Suffolk Library Institute" program, May 11, 1983.
    [112] Promotional brochure for Path to Power, June 1983.
    [113] "LBJ's One Great Indiscretion," Sydney Morning Herald, April 16, 1983.
    [114] Invitation, tickets, program to Caro's honorary doctorate ceremony, Merrimack College, May 22, 1983.
    [115] "Pulitzer Prize winner to speak at Law Day Banquet," Austin Lawyers Journal, March 1983.
    [116] Letter from Michael Grossberg, Secretary, Free Press Association, undated.
    [117] "Robert A. Caro. Featured Speaker at the First General Session Texas Library Association Conference, April 24, 1985."
    [118a] Photo of Caro in Publishers Weekly, May 9, 1986.
    [118b] Inside Bookselling, April 14, 1986.
    [118c] Elizabeth Mehren, "A Passion for Print at This Book-of-the-Month Gala," Los Angeles Times, April 21, 1986.
    [118d] Lauren Long, "BOMC's 60th Anniversary Party," F.Y.I., April 28, 1986.
    [118e] "Birthday book," Women's Wear Daily, April 23, 1986.
    [118f] "The Book-of-the-Month Club Turns the Page to its 60th Birthday.. .," People, May 4, 1986.
    [118g] Susan Heller Anderson and David Bird, "Reading for Pleasure," New York Times, April 19, 1986.
    [118h] Charles E. Claffey, "Book of the Month Club marks 60 years," Boston Globe, April 21, 1986.
    [119] Brief bio of Caro.
  - Scrapbook 9, 1982-1987 (Box [XI-07])
    Spine embossed "1984" and "9"; labeled "12/4/83-5/22/86." Contains reviews and publicity of The Years of Lyndon Johnson: The Path to Power.
    [01] Library of Congress Information Bulletin, vol. 42, no. 50 (December 12, 1983).
    [02] "Reading for Work and Pleasure," New York Times Book Review, December 4, 1983.
    [03] Advertisement for The Path to Power, Book World, December 4, 1983.
    [04] John Gabree, "LBJ and Elvis in Paperback," Sunday Newsday, Books, December 4, 1983.
    [05] Michael Kernan, "The Art of Writing a Life," Washington Post, November 14, 1983.
    [06] Raymond A. Schroth, "Biographer as Bloodhound," Commonweal, April 22, 1983.
    [07-09] Paul Gordon, "Diseased Appetite," Reason, May 1983.
    [08a] Charlotte Curtis, "Love Affair With the City," New York Times, October 18, 1983.
    [10] Press release, Free Press Association, mentioning Path to Power won Mencken Award for best book, undated.
    [11] "Authors Meet 'Bobcat," Publishers Weekly, October 21, 1983. [Photo of Caro with Isaac Asimov, Joseph Lash, and Carlton Rockwell using NYU's new online library catalog.]
    [12] Maurice A. Frank, "Johnson biography bares many details," Chicago Daily Law Bulletin, March 16, 1983.
    [13] Bill Beck, "Book on LBJ rated among finest political biographies of century," Duluth, Minnesota News-Tribune & Herald, May 8, 1983.
    [14] Tom Chadwick, "Johnson portrait a vivid picture of the president," Augusta Chronicle-Herald, May 2, 1983.
    [15-16] James T. Patterson, review of Path to Power, Journal of American History, undated.
    [17] William Goldstein, "Robert Caro's long path to biographies of power," Book Week, [Chicago?] Sun-Times, January 1, 1984.
    [18-19] Bryan Woolley, "Weathering the storm: LBJ biographer is proud book survived critics' attacks," Dalla Times Herald, January 12, 1984.
    [20] Sharon O'Malley, "Researching a President's 'Path to Power'," Rural Electric News Service, 1983 [profile of Ina Caro].
    [21] Page from unidentified NYU periodical with a photo similar to "Authors Meet Bobcat" [see scrapbook p. 11].
    [22a] Photograph of Caro, presumably at English-Speaking Union of the United States (16 East 69th Street, New York, N.Y.), April 1984.
    [22b] Card, "With the Compliments of the English-Speaking Union of the United States.. .," April 18, 1984.
    [23] Letter from Mike Driscoll, Harris County (Texas) Attorney, April 7, 1986.
    [24] David Burner, review of Path to Power, American Historical Review, December 1983.
    [25] Hugh Davis Graham, review of Path to Power, Journal of Southern History, vol. 50, no 1 (February 1984).
    [26] James Kaufmann, "Between soft covers," Christian Science Monitor Book Review, February 3, 1984.
    [27] "Quote-Acrostic," Chicago Tribune, April 27, 1986.
    [28-29] James T. Patterson, review of Path to Power, Journal of American History, undated.
    [30] Col. Rpbert G. Clarke, review of Path to Power, Military Review, November 1983.
    [31] "Caro, Robert A.," entry in Contemporary Authors.
    [32] Letter from Murray Wolf, June 29, 1984.
    [33] Caricature of Robert Moses standing on Verrazzano-Narrows Bridge.
    [34] Caricature of Lyndon B. Johnson with another man [singing].
    [35] "Nonfiction Reprints," in unidentified trade periodical, October 14, 1983.
    [36] Nicholas von Hoffman, "Watergate Under the Bridge," New Republic, July 16 & 23, 1984.
    [37] Cynthia Werthamer, "Joe Pulitzer's Gift," Columbia Magazine, June 1984.
    [38] "YOUR NAME APPEARS IN THIS ISSUE OF CURRENT BIOGRAPHY".
    [39] Authors Guild Bulletin, Winter 1984.
    [40] Roscoe Drummond, "Bigger-than-life portrait of LBJ," [?] Review, December 3, 1982.
    [41] Steven Thomma, "Author of 'Path to Power' portrays an unpolished LBJ," unidentified, undated newspaper.
    [42] [blank]
    [43] Lou Gelfand, "New LBJ biography devastating commentary on American politics," unidentified Minnesota[?] newspapers, December 19, 1982.
    [44-45a] Sam Newlund, "Author of shocking LBJ biography feels pity, not hate, for his subject," Minneapolis Star and Tribune, December 20, 1982.
    [45b] Letter from "Grant" on Century Association letterhead, October 6, 1984.
    [45c] Tear sheet from The Century Bulletin listing Caro's talk on "Learning about Lyndon Johnson," October 4, 1984.
    [46] Eliot Fremont-Smith, "Judging LBJ," Village Voice, November 30, 1982.
    [47] Rick Soll, "LBJ: Political Myth and Down-Home Reality," [Chicago?] Sun-Times, December 15, 1982.
    [48] Advertisement for Caro's October 23, 1984 lecture, "The Presidency of Lyndon Baines Johnson," at the 92nd Street Y, New York Times, September 9, 1984.
    [49] "Public Access," New York Times, April 16, 1985.
    [50] Princeton Alumni Weekly clipping, class of '57 news of Caro, July 10, 1985.
    [51] Alan Wolfe, "'I, Koch': A campaign biography—in reverse," unidentified newspaper, August 26, 1985.
    [52] Eva Hoffman, "Biography as Art Form Discussed by Writers," New York Times, November 19, 1984.
    [53] David Maister, "Beyond Garbage-Can Decision Making," unidentified, undated periodical.
    [54-55] Rebeca [sic] Zimmermann, "Library sets author dinner," Waco Tribune-Herald, September 2, 1985.
    [56] Mike Cox, "Caro pursues LBJ with passion," Austin American Statesman, April 22, 1984 [copy 1].
    [57] Steven Waldman, "Put the Politics Back Into Political Science," Washington Monthly, September 1985.
    [58] Mike Cox, "Caro pursues LBJ with passion," Austin American Statesman, April 22, 1984 [copy 2].
    [59] Rebeca [sic] Zimmermann, "Caro surmounts obstacles," Waco Tribune-Herald, October 4, 1985.
    [60] New York Times crossword puzzle, October 9, 1985. Clue 29 down: "Robert Moses biographer."
    [61] [blank]
    [62] Marsha Westfall, "LBJ biographer to lecture," Waco Tribune-Herald, September 1, 1985.
    [63a] Rebeca [sic] Zimmermann, "Texas challenges noted author," Waco Tribune-Herald, October 4, 1985 [2 copies].
    [63b] Rebeca [sic] Zimmermann, "Caro surmounts obstacles," Waco Tribune-Herald, October 4, 1985.
    [64] "Friends of the Waco-McLennan County Library Second Annual Author Dinner, October 3, 1985, Featured Speaker Robert A. Caro," with Caro's entry from "Current Biography Yearbook 1984."
    [65] [blank]
    [66] James Fallows, "The New Celebrities of Washington," New York Review of Books, June 12, 1986.
    [67] Michael Kramer, "Manes, The Mess, and the Mayor," New York Magazine, February 10, 1986.
    [68] Barbara Ross, "Has our number. There was Fiorello, then Wagner & now Koch is 3d to score 3 times," New York Daily News, November 6, 1985.
    [69-70] William P. Barrett, "The path to LBJ," Dallas Times Herald, November 14, 1985.
    [71] Photocopy of photograph with note identifying "Clockwise, from left: Frank Johnson, Stan Hinden[?], John Cummings, Dick Zander, Leo Seligsohn, Dave Kahn, Jim Hadjin".
    [72] Invitation: "Chancellor and Mrs. Richard L. Van Horn cordially invite you to a dinner in honor of Mr. Robert A. Caro, Tenneco Distinguished Lecturer," March 19, 1986. With brochure for lecture.
    [73a] Samuel G. Freedman, "A Film Maker Documents the Huey Long Era," New York Times, February 25, 1986.
    [73b] Letter from Ric Burns, Florentine Filmes, April 21, 1986.
    [74] Stephanie A. McGrath, "Frontier spirit can save city, author states," Houston Chronicle, March 20, 1986.
    [75] "Famous Author Visits Bonham," The Majority Report of the Friends of Sam Rayburn, undated.
    [76] "Sam Rayburn: a speaker and a man like no other," Greenville Herald Banner, Thursday, March 13, 1986.
    [77] Dave McNeely, "Writer finished research for second book on LBJ," Austin American-Statesman, April 2, 1986.
    [78] [blank].
    [79-81] George DeWan, "A Tenuous Place in History," Newsday, Part II, April 8, 1986.
    [82-83] David McCullough, "I Love Washington," American Heritage, April-May 1986.
    [84-85] Book-of-the-Month Club 60th anniversary dinner invitation and program, with letter to Caro from Al Silverman, chairman, March 21, 1986.
    [86] Letter from "Mom" to "Sid," April 14, 1986.
    [87] Photo of Caro with Dr. Lewis Thomas, Toni Morrison, and Al Silverman at Book-of-the-Month Club 60th anniversary, Publishers Weekly, May 9, 1986.
    [88a] "Extraordinary Lives: The Art and Craft of American Biography," Publishers Weekly, May 16, 1986.
    [88b] "BOMC's 60th Anniversary Party," f.y.i., April 28, 1986.
    [89] [blank].
    [90a] Ben Kubasik, Susan Mulcahy, and Anthony Scaduto, "TV City Reception Poor on West Side," Newsday, May 22, 1986.
    [90b] David Kahn, "Mining the Riches of the NY Public Library," Newsday, May 22, 1986.
    [91] Peter Baida, "The Corrupting of New York City," American Heritage, December 1986.
    [92a] "Literary Academy Announces Awards," Washington Post, undated.
    [92b] "Prizes for write staff," Newsday, April 7, 1986.
    [92c]"17 Writers Honored By Academy-Institute," New York Times, April 4, 1986.
    [93] Advertisement, "1986 Awards, American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, Robert A. Caro, author of The Years of Lyndon Johnson: The Path to Power," New York Times, May 22, 1986 [2 copies], with sticker of same.
    [94] Letter from Alfred Kazin, Chairman, Awards Committee for Literature, American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, February 11, 1986.
    [95] "Citation, Robert A. Caro," American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, 1986.
    [96] Program, "American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, Exhibition of Work by Newly Elected members and Recipients of Awards," May 21-June 15, 1986.
    [97] American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, 1986 Award in Literature, Robert A. Caro" [copy].
    [98] Deirdre Donahue, "The new chief at 'The New Yorker'," USA Today, undated.
    [99a] Richard Johnson, "Whodunit," New York Post, March 21, 1987.
    [99b] Seth Kantor, "LBJ biographer Caro resurrecting ghosts of Senates past," Austin American Statesman, March 28, 1987.
    [100] Karal Ann Marlin, "He Did Not Hear the Mermaids," New York Times Book Review, April 12, 1987.
    [101] "Caro, Herman, and Lewis Headline the Centennial Saturday Program," Horace Mann-Barnard School Centennial Year News, February 1, 1987, Report #3.
  - Scrapbook [10], 1983-1990 (+1959) (Box [XI-07])
    Spine embossed "0" (10?) with "1987" label. Contains a mix of Power Broker and LBJ material.
    [Numbers in brackets represent the pages of the scrapbook. Pages containing more than one item are marked by "a," "b," etc.]
    [01] American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, 1986 Award in Literature, Robert A. Caro" [copy].
    [02a] "Nation's book critics honor Caro for Lyndon Johnson biography," Riverdale Press, February 10, 1983.
    [02b] George Leopold, "N.Y. World's Fair lingering failure," Waterbury (Connecticut) Republican, May 18, 1984.
    [03] Eva Hoffman, "Biography as Art Form Discussed by Writers," New York Times, November 19, 1984.
    [04a] Flyer, "WNYC AM/83 presents The New York Public Library's Three-part lecture series: 'Robert A. Caro on the Making of New York'," May 20-22, [1987].
    [04b] "Public Programs, Spring 1987, The New York Public Library."
    [05] David Kahn, "Mining the Riches of the NY Public Library," Newsday, May 22, 1986.
    [06] Ben Kubasik, Susan Mulcahy, and Anthony Scaduto, "TV City Reception Poor on West Side," Newsday, May 22, 1986.
    [07] Review of Extraordinary Lives: The Art and Craft of American Biography, "Brussat's Book Notes," Cultural Information Services, August 11, 1986.
    [08] Thomas Mallon, "From the lives of the great biographers," U.S.A. Today, July 25, 1986.
    [09] Steve Paul, "Truman biographer gets close to the source," Kansas City Star, July 27, 1986.
    [10] Milton Lomask, "The art and craft of plumbing 'the abysmal depths of personality'," Houston Post, July 27, 1986.
    [11] Announcement of Caro's award from American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters in Princeton Alumni Weekly, October 15, 1986.
    [12] "The Makers of New York," WNYC Program Guide, May 1987.
    [13] E. R. Shipp, "Judge Under a Cloud. Hortense Wittstein Gabel," New York Times, June 12, 1987.
    [14] Lori B. Miller, "Authors Seek Muse In a Room," New York Times, August 2, 1987.
    [15a] Photograph of the Caros and others during session of the Sag Harbor Initiative, East Hampton Star, August 6, 1987.
    [15b] Michael Moss, "The book they're all talking about," August 24, 1987.
    [16] Deirdre Donahue, "The new chief at 'The New Yorker'," USA Today, undated.
    [17] Jessie Mangaliman, "Westpride Wants to Shrink TV City," Newsday, October 2, 1987.
    [18a] Ronnie Wacker, "A 'New National Strategy'," New York Times, undated.
    [18b] Photo of Caro speaking, East Hampton Star, August 27, 1987.
    [19] Michael Fleming, Karen Freifeld, and Susan Mulcahy, "Look Down in Anger," unidentified, undated periodical.
    [20a] "Trump battles 'selfish' celebrities," New York Post, September 11, 1987.
    [20b] "Upper West Side / Westpride Throws Fete to Fight Trump," Newsday, September 18, 1987.
    [21] "Robert A. Caro On Television City: Who Is Representing the Public?" Excerpt from a statement by Caro at Westpride benefit on September 29, 1987.
    [22] Liz Smith, "Literati turn out for the write cause," Daily News, October 25, 1987.
    [23] Kathy Larkin, "Party line for people who party," October 25, 1987.
    [24] Bob Herbert, "Robert Caro v. Television City," Daily News, October 20, 1987.
    [25-26] Tom Allon, "Columbus Circle Project: Celevs vs. The Shadow," West Side Spirit, October 26, 1987.
    [27 & 29] "Experts Say that TV City would Be an Isolated Suburb," New York Observer, November 2, 1987 [partial article].
    [28] Frank Sommerfield, "Trump's West Side finesse. Developer deals, trades—a bit—to gain approval for Television City," Crain's New York Business, November 2, 1987.
    [30] Tom Robbins, "The Bard vs. the Mayor," New York Observer, November 9, 1987.
    [31] Brendan Gill, "The Sky Line. On the Brink," The New Yorker, November 9, 1987.
    [32] Sydney H. Schanberg, "Mort Zuckerman Runs into a Den of Grizzlies," unidentified, undated newspaper.
    [33] Deirdre Donahue, "The new chief at 'The New Yorker'," USA Today, February 16, 1987.
    [34] "Private Life, Public Office. What must voters know about a candidate for President?," Time, May 18, 1987. Includes photo of Caro with quote.
    [35] Bonnie Angelo, "Troubled Times for Hizzoner," Time, November 30, 1987.
    [36] Jane Gross, "2 Big West Side Projects Fuel Anti-Development Sentiment," New York Times, November 29, 1987.
    [37] Princeton Alumni Weekly, November 25, 1987. Clipping with news of Caro, class of '57.
    [38-39a] Ginger Danto, "Observer Poll Finds Koch Rates High, Trump Popular," New York Observer, December 21, 1987.
    [39-b] Polaroid photos of Ina(?) and Robert Caro.
    [40-41] Bonnie Angelo, "Troubled Times for Hizzoner," Time, November 30, 1987.
    [43] Paul Bogaards to Robert Caro, schedule of interviews and appearances in connection with publication of Means of Ascent, March 16, 1990.
    [44-46] David Remnick, "Johnson's Boswell: Robert A. Caro learns what it means to hitch one's life to another man's history," Texas Monthly, February 1988.
    [47] David Lida, "Robert Caro: The Power Writer," Women's Wear Daily, February 1, 1988.
    [48-49] Four pages of a published conversation between "Mr. Platt" and "Mr. Wood" discussing Robert Moses and the early activities of the Municipal Art Society.
    [50] "A recycled anecdote about Cuomo," Page Six, New York Post, March 1, 1988.
    [51] David W. Dunlap, "Marking the Dual Legacy of Robert Moses," New York Times, December 14, 1988.
    [52] Advertisement for Power Broker in conjunction with Moses' centennial, New York Times, December 14, 1988.
    [53] Ira Wolfman, "The Savage, Ferocious Drive to Get Things Done. Reflections on Robert Moses in the Master Builder's centennial year," Daily News Magazine, December 18, 1988.
    [54] Maurice Carroll, "Inglorious End to the Career of Respected Judge," Newsday, December 23, 1988.
    [55] Ridgely Ochs, "Robert Caro: The Biographer's Reflection," Newsday, December 4, 1988.
    [56] The Livable City: A Publication of the Municipal Art Society, December 1988. Issue devoted to Robert Moses.
    [57] James Atlas, "Speaking Ill of the Dead," New York Times Magazine, November 6, 1988.
    [58] Arnold H. Lubasch, "Defense Calls 5 In Myerson Case Before Resting," New York Times, December 7, 1988.
    [59] Mary Hilliard photo of Robert and Ina(?) Caro with another man and woman.
    [60] "Pen Central," W, May 30-June 6, 1988. Includes photo of Caro at PEN Gala in New York.
    [61] Robert A. Caro, "Starting Late, Finishing First," New York Times, June 12, 1988.
    [62] Robert A. Caro, "His Was a Banner Held High," Vineyard Gazette, Martha's Vineyard, June 17, 1988.
    [63] Polaroid photo of Ina(?) Caro.
    [64] Christopher Lehmann-Haupt, "Re-examining the New Deal and Its Architects," New York Times, June 13, 1988. With note: "This review is in Bob's scrapbook because, if Bob hadn't called Lehmann-Haupt, Chris would not have read the book."
    [66] Benjamin Forgey, "Robert Moses, Builder of An Era," Washington Post, January 10, 1989.
    [67] Seth Kantor, "Author shares LBJ's secrets with Capitol Hill crowd," Austin American-Statesman, February 11, 1989.
    [68] Richard Bernstein, "Passages in Defense of a Colleague: Writers Read and Speak for Rushdie," February 23, 1989.
    [69] W, March 21-28, 1988, "CORRECTION / Robert Caro's book 'The Path to Power' was sold as a potential miniseries for $1 million. The figure given in a story on page 22, March 7-14, was incorrect."
    [70] Letter, Edward C. Smith, Office of Minority Affairs, American University, Washington, D.C., March 21, 1988.
    [71] Edward C. Smith, "Robert Moses: 'Emperor' of the Empire State," unidentified, undated publication.
    [72] Mike Cox, "LBJ biographer delves into Austin records," Austin American-Statesman, April 3, 1988.
    [73] Elizabeth Bennett, "LBJ biographer digging even deeper into his subject," Houston Post, April 17, 1988.
    [74] [blank]
    [75] Polaroid photos of Rober and Ina(?) Caro.
    [76] Glenn Collins, "Partylock at Elaine's: 25 Years of First Names," New York Times, April 26, 1988.
    [77] Fox Butterfield, "Is Life in New York City Really Getting Worse?," New York Times, March 10, 1989.
    [78] David Lida, "Robert Caro: The Subject is Power," W, March 7-14, 1988.
    [79] Seth Kantor, "Author shares LBJ's secrets with Capitol Hill crowd," Austin American-Statesman, February 11, 1989.
    [80] Ann Marie Lipinski, "Lawrence Bloom: In Chicago, being Mr. Clean can soil a candidate's image," unidentified Chicago-area newspaper, undated.
    [81] "Noted author Robert Caro to present 8th Prichard Lecture at annual dinner," University of Kentucky, Library News and Information, vol. 1, no. 2 (Winter 1989).
    [82] Freedom-to-Write Bulletin, March 1989. Includes Caro's statement in support of Salman Rushdie, 5-6.
    [83] Geraldine Fabrikant, "Eagerly Embracing Roseland, Writers and Old Money Dine and Dance," New York Times, April 27, 1989.
    [85a] Ken Auletta, "The Little Flower and How He Grew," New York Times, October 15, 1989.
    [85b] Three color photos of a Texas (San Jose?) billboard advertising The Path to Power, December, 1983.
    [86] Christopher Gray, "Streetscapes: Readers' Question," New York Times, May 28, 1989. Question about Manhattan's P.S. 93, "Where Bob went to school."
    [87] "KOCH: a New York state of mind," unidentified, undated publication.
    [88] "Russian Around," Women's Wear Daily, June 1, 1989.
    [89] Bob Caro, "A Troubled Man Pickets Kin, Then Tries, Suicide," unidentified publication, September 19, 1959.
    [90a] Nicholas Lemann, "Little John," Atlantic Monthly, October 1989.
    [90b] Dick Oliver, "An 'Interview' With The Late Master Builder," West Side Spirit, Through September 3, 1989.
    [91] E. J. Dionne Jr., "History's Sliding Scale of Ethics in the Capital," New York Times, April 21, 1989.
    [92] Frank Rose, "Celebrity Zoning. They're fighting glitz with glitz to foil Donald Trump's grand designs on the Upper West Side," Manhattan, Inc., October 1989.
    [inside back cover] Eight loose photographs of Caro's son(?) (April 1959) and grandson(?) (1987).
  - Scrapbook [11], 1989-1990 (Box [XI-08])
    Spine labeled "New Yorker 1989." Covers The Years of Lyndon Johnson: The Path to Power and Means of Ascent.
    [01] [blank]
    [02] "Crew mate: Nothing heroic in LBJ award," Tribune, November 3, 1989.
    [03] Robert A. Caro, "Annals of Politics. The Johnson Years: Buying and Selling," The New Yorker, December 18, 1989 (complete issue).
    [04] Robert A. Caro, "Annals of Politics. The Johnson Years: The Old and The New. I—The Opponent," The New Yorker, January 15, 1990 (complete issue).
    [05] Robert A. Caro, "Annals of Politics. The Johnson Years: The Old and The New. II—Whirlwind," The New Yorker, January 22, 1990 (complete issue).
    [06] Robert A. Caro, "Annals of Politics. The Johnson Years: The Old and The New. III—All or Nothing," The New Yorker, January 29, 1990 (complete issue).
    [07] Robert A. Caro, "Annals of Politics. The Johnson Years: The Old and The New. IV—The Stealing," The New Yorker, February 5, 1990 (complete issue).
    [08-10] [blank]
    [11a] Letter (on card), Robert K. Massie, February 8, 1990.
    [11b] Publication announcement for Means of Ascent, Book World, October 15, 1989.
    [12-13] [blank]